SELENA RAMIREZ

A Corporate Trainer with eight years of experience specializing in hospitality management, program development, curriculum design, and e-learning. A strong history of developing and implementing quality training programs to enhance custom er service del ivery.

123 Bedford Avenue, New York, NY, 12345 se lena rami rez@examp le. com (123)456-7890

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

TRAINER

Hilton Hotels, New York, NY June 2016 -Present

deliver seminars to over 150+ managers and team members on customer service best practices and standards, resulting in a 30% increase in guest satisfaction scores

Design, develop, and implement training curriculum fora premiere hotel chain,

- Conduct comprehensive audits of performance data, design training programs to improve upselling and rewards memberships, and increase enrollments by up to 20%
- Create coursesand training curriculum for team members pursuing leadership and managem ent opportuni ties with in the organization

TRAINER

Hotel Marriot, New York, NY July 2013-June 2016

- Del ivered com prehensive tra i n i ng sem i nars for ove r 80+ new h i res o n booki n g software, company POS, customer service standards, and guest relations
- Provided training to hotel managers on operations management approaches and employee engagement programs to maximize operational performance

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science (B.S.) Business Administration

University of Syracuse, New York, NY Septem be r 2009 - May 2013

KEY SKILLS

- Hospita I i ty M a n agem e nt
- Adult Learning
- ♦ Curriculum Design
- ♦ Staff Development
- ♦ Program Development

CERTIFICATIONS

◆ Certified Professional in Training Management (CPTM), 2013